(Amy:)What are you talking about?
(Sheldon:)Oh, there's this company
(Sheldon:)that's attempting
to establish a colony on Mars,
(Sheldon:)and I applied
to be among the first to go.
(Sheldon:)What should
we name him?
(Sheldon:)You know, I came in
thinking "Seth," but...
(Sheldon:)he kind of looks Italian.
(Amy:)You applied for a mission
(Amy:)to be a colonist
on another planet,
(Amy:)and couldn't be bothered
to tell me?
(Sheldon:)Would you have approved?
(Amy:)Of course not.
(Sheldon:)Well, based on
your reaction,
(Sheldon:)it looks like I made
the right choice.
(Sheldon:)Isn't that right, Giuseppe?
(Leonard:)Hey, hey.
Listen, I-I have a little
confession to make.
(Penny:)Aw, is this your first time?
(Leonard:)No, I got you something
for Valentine's Day,
(Leonard:)and I was too embarrassed
to give it to you.
(Penny:)Well, why?
(Leonard:)Well, 'cause I got it
at the dirty store.